Guide to the Cornell Plantations records, [ca. 1945]-1999
Cornell Plantations records
- Series II. Oversized plans, maps and drawings
  - No. 165: [map of part of the Arboretum] Sheet 1; R. Mower, 1964 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 166: Cornell University, Agricultural Econ. Shrub Garden; F.W.S., May 30, 1934 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 167: Proposed 12" Culvert across NYS Highway #392; J. E. Miller, November 27, 1938 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 168: [unidentified acetate of part of the arboretum(?) with one pond, some sycamores, basswoods, twin elm and many numbers 1/4 148 or more 1/2], n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 169: Cornell Plantations; General Plant Groupings for Arboretum, n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 170: Cornell Plantations; Pedestrian Footbridge, October 1970 November 1970 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 171: Cornell Plantations; Handrail Study for Vehicular Bridge, November 3, 1970 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 172: Cornell Plantations; [elevation of part of arboretum] 1D, November 3, 1970 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 173: Cornell Plantations; [elevations and plantings adjacent to Plantations Road], 2D, November 3, 1970 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - [The next four maps are stapled together]
  - No. 174: Cornell Plantations, Alignment and Construction Plan, GC-2, n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 175: Cornell Plantations, Alignment and Construction Plan, G 3, n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 176: Cornell Plantations, Alignment and Construction Plan, G 4, n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 177: Cornell Plantations, Alignment and Construction Plan, G 5 [numbered in back upper left corner], n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - [The next four maps are stapled together]
  - No. 178: Cornell Plantations; Planting Development, PD-1, n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 179: Cornell Plantations; Planting Development, PD-2, n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 180: Cornell Plantations; Planting Development, PD-3, n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 181: Cornell Plantations; Planting Development, PD-4/5 [numbered in back upper left corner], n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - [The next 14 maps (182-195) are stapled together]
  - No. 182: Cornell Plantations; Planting Development PD-1; [the basis of this map is 178; partly pencilled in, partly colored and numbered] revision, April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 183: Cornell Plantations; Planting Development PD-2, April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 184: Cornell Plantations; Planting Development PD-3, April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 185: Cornell Plantations; Planting Development PD-4/5, April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 186: Cornell Plantations; Grading, Storm Drainage, Plumbing and Electrical Plan; GC-2A, April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 187: Cornell Plantations; Grading, Storm Drainage, Plumbing and Electrical Plan; GC-2B, April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 188: Cornell Plantations; Grading, Storm Drainage, Plumbing and Electrical Plan; GC-2C, April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 189: Cornell Plantations; Grading, Storm Drainage, Plumbing and Electrical Plan; GC-3B, April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 190: Cornell Plantations; Grading, Storm Drainage, Plumbing and Electrical Plan; GC-3C, April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 191: Cornell Plantations; Grading, Storm Drainage, Plumbing and Electrical Plan; GC-3D, April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 192: Cornell Plantations; Grading, Storm Drainage, Plumbing and Electrical Plan, GC-4A, April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 193: Cornell Plantations; Grading, Storm Drainage, Plumbing and Electrical Plan, GC-4B, April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 194: Cornell Plantations; Grading, Storm Drainage, Plumbing and Electrical Plan, GC-5A, April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 195: Cornell Plantations; Grading, Storm Drainage, Plumbing and Electrical Plan, GC-5B [numbered in upper left corner], April 21, 1973 (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 196: Cornell Plantations; Site Grading and Drainage, SK-1, n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 196a: [same as 196], n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 197: Cornell Plantations; Site Grading and Drainage, SK-2, n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 197a: [same as 197], n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 198: Cornell Plantations; Planting Development, PD-1, n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 199: Cornell Plantations; Planting Development, PD-2, n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 200: Cornell Plantations; Planting Development, PD-3 [198-200 are basically the same as 178-180], n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 201: [unidentified map showing plantings(?) along one part of Arboretum Road(?) on tracing paper, badly torn], n.d. (Map-case Folder 11)
  - No. 202: [map of Cornell, part of Ithaca and part of Tompkins County; inked on tracing paper, badly crumpled and torn], n.d. (Map-case Folder 12)
  - No. 203: Plan of the Cornell Arboretum [pencil note on back: N. M. Wells map], n.d. (Map-case Folder 12)
  - No. 204: Plan of Development of Cascadilla Gorge, E. Gorton Davis, Dept. of Landscape Architecture at Cornell [numbered in back upper left corner], June 1926 (Map-case Folder 12)
  - No. 205-226: Cornell University; Key Plan; Original Data from Department Files, Additional Files, Additional Data from R. N. Fitzpatrick, September 2, 1960 (Map-case Folder 12)
    [these 22 maps are quadrants which form one large map when numbered sides are matched up]; Factory Mutual Engineering Division, Associated Factory Mutual Fire Insturance Cos. Norwood, Mass; Index No. 27015; serial numbers 51301-51322
  - Additional plans including drawings/sketches, proposed additions, proposed Marks Conservatory and Laboratory, proposed glass enclosures, sea watch towers, boiler room, etc.; also unidentified group photo of students looking at tree, ca. 1968-1976 (Map-case Folder 13)
  - Fernow Hall, 1973-1978 (Map-case Folder 14)
  - Arboretum plans, 1936 (Map-case Folder 14)
  - Fish rearing pond at fish hatcheries plans, 1937 (Map-case Folder 14)
  - Parking overlook north of Pit Greenhouse, 1959 (Map-case Folder 14)
  - Cross sections, n.d. (Map-case Folder 14)
  - Location plan - new creek channel, 1939 (Map-case Folder 14)
  - Details for dam - Cascadilla Creek - east of ROTC stables, 1937 (Map-case Folder 14)
  - Bridge details - Cascadilla Creek, 1937 (Map-case Folder 14)
  - 26 plans concerning planting development; general site plans; grading, storm drainage, plumbing and electrical; other construction details, n.d. (Map-case Folder 15)
    [these are larger plans]